ARYN WEATHERLY

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT

Energetic, hard-working and resilient. Lover of books, science, puzzles, art and video games. I attended school for massage therapy, radiology technology and physical therapy. I spent many years working in the health field only to realize I wanted to do something else with my life. It wasn't until a friend suggested I look into programming that really felt I found what I was meant to do for the rest of my life

CONTACT INFO

PHONE: (615) 428-4487

FMAII:

Arynweatherly93@gmail.com

GITHUB

https://github.com/Arynweatherly

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/arynweatherly

EDUCATION

Nashville Software School

• Full Stack Web Development

University of Tennessee at Chattanooga

BS Exercise Science

Brenau University

• Physical Therapy Program

WORK EXPERIENCE

SALON CAPELLI DAY SPA AND BOUTIOUE

Receptionist | 2011 - 2015

- Customer services, sales metrics,
- Tasked with pricing products, scheduling appointments and managing finances
- Opened and closed the store each day

X-CLUSIVE BOUTIQUE

Sales associate and Model | 2012 -2013

 Tasked with organizing the store, managing finances, pricing products and modeling clothes for the website.

PERSONAL TRAINER

Personal Trainer | 2016 - 2017

- Tasked with helping clients change their lives for the better through exercise programs and diet plans.
- Created individualized workout schedules, assisted and instructed clients on how to properly use workout equipment
- Motivated and encouraged clients.

BEADED BUNGALOW

Sales Associate and Designerl | 2019 -present

- Worked closely with clients to create one of a kind pieces of jewelry.
- Reapaired broken pieces.

JEWELRY BY ARYN

Owner and Designer | 2018 -present

- Manage finances, inventory, social media presence, and personal website.
- Designed, created and sold one of a kind pieces of jewelry to clients.

TECH EXPERIENCE

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL

Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp

Group projects:

Welcome to Nashville

- Team based project centered around creating itineraries for select groups of tourist through utilization of several different APIs.
- Utilized Zomato API to render a list of restaurants to the DOM and saved client's choice in restaurant to their itinerary.
- Styled the website with CSS.
- Main language used: Javascript

Nutshell/React

- Team based project that involved building a dashboard application to display a user's friends, messages, tasks, events, and news articles.
- Used React.js and Reactstrap to build and style the project.
- Each aspect of the application utilized CRUD functionality.
- Wire framing and planning were completed with db diagram and mockflow.

Front-End Capstone

Pass a Note

- Note sharing application built with React.Js.
- Utilized Adobe and Adobe XD to build all graphics used in the application.
- Used CSS, Bootstrap, and Bulma to style the login, registration, home page and all
- Used Cloudinary to provide users with the ability to upload images.